Ah! Fuck. Yeah, it doesn't matter.
Whoa. You okay there, Richard?
Uh, yeah, I'm fine.
Sorry, I can't really throw it any slower.
Give it another cut, Richard.
No, I'm fine. I don't want to.
Maybe someone else wants to. Who's next?
If someone has to go, I'll go,
but it seems very frightening.
You sure? You got us for the whole hour.
- Anyone?
- Would it hurt your feelings if no one went?
Man on P.A.: Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the annual
Stern-Taylor fall classic.
I'd like to start by making a toast
to our very special guest tonight,
Richard Hendricks.
Richard, after your perfect game
at TechCrunch Disrupt a few weeks ago,
we fell in love with you and your tech.
Look, we know everyone in
the Valley is after you,
and we know that you're probably
going to go with Peter Gregory,
but we'd love to have you
come play on our team.
Let Stern-Taylor Capital Fund
in on your Series A financing,
because together, Richard, we'd be...
a home... run!
- Oh, right.
- What do you say, Richard?
I'll... I'll do what I can.
All right.
Have fun, everybody.
I don't know, man. It's
starting to feel weird
letting all these firms suck up to us, even
though we're not gonna take their money.
Richard, Peter Gregory hasn't
officially given us the term sheet yet.
Yes, but he will tomorrow when he gets back.
If you can't enjoy this many people
kissing our ass at this level,
then I feel sorry for you.
Would you just relax and
take it in for a second?
I mean, we are getting our
dicks sucked at the AT&T Park.
We're standing on the field
of the World Series champions.
- It's totally lost on me.
- Yeah, I don't give a shit, either.
Hey! I'm Nicole Stein.
I lead the Growth Team at Stern-Taylor.
- Oh, I'm Dinesh.
- I'm Gilfoyle.
I love it. So what do
you two do at Pied Piper?
- I'm the CTO.
- Ha ha, he's joking. I'm the CTO.
Fuck you, I'm joking.
Okay, how could you be the
Chief Technology Officer?
I get it. You hear the word "chief,"
and you think "Indian Chief."
- but you're the other kind of Indian.
- Okay. One, Fuck you.
I'm Pakistani. And two, how
could you be CTO of anything?
You have to be able to organize, you have to
be able to delegate, and you have to be...